Allow me to introduce you to Itana. She's an Instagram model from Barcelona who's been going viral,
but she's also just like totally chilling down to earth. She's into fitness and video games,
and yeah, if you're wondering, she does have additional photos on our subscription tier,
which brings in about 10 grand per month. Before you sign up though, there's one thing I need to
disclose, and it really shouldn't matter unless you're some kind of bigot technophobic Nazi,
but she's not a biological female. She is a woman, but entirely artificial. It is November 29th,
2023, and you're watching the code report. By the end of this video, you'll know how to build
your own army of AI influencers, entirely for free using open source generative image models like
stable diffusion XL and checkpoints like juggernaut that can produce highly realistic images. The first
generative adversarial networks appeared about 10 years ago, and at first could only produce tiny
images that you could barely make out. But now anyone can produce high resolution realistic images
good enough to trick sad lonely men into buying the NSFW content. It's extremely sad and depressing
that the agency behind this thing is making a six figure income, especially during the sacred
month of no nut November. Content like this is rotting the brains of billions of men around the
world. Although they are doing a 50% off sale right now, so it does look like a pretty good value
actually. Luckily 95% of this channel is comprised of high value alpha males, which means we don't
need to consume content like that. Instead, we reverse engineer it so we can exploit it for
financial gain. There are many tools out there that can help you become an AI PIMP, like you might be
familiar with mid journey and dolly from open AI, but these are paid close source products that
also contain a bunch of unwanted safety layers. Luckily, there's a great open source ecosystem
around generative AI. The most well known base model is stable diffusion XL, which was released
in late July 2023. Gigantic models like this take an absurd amount of computing power, but luckily
it's possible to fine tune them by creating what's called a checkpoint using some additional
specialized training data. Now you don't have to worry about this part because people have already
created a bunch of different checkpoints, which you can find on websites like civet AI, some of which
are highly optimized for photo realism. Now the next part of the puzzle is finding a UI where we
can actually work with these models without having to write any code. The most well known option is
the stable diffusion web UI. It's an incredibly powerful tool, but might be a little overwhelming
for a beginner. There's just a lot of different buttons to push. Another cool option is comfy UI,
which has a drag and drop editor that works kind of like blender or Unreal Engine. But the one I'm
using in this video is focus or focus, and I'll explain why I like it in just a minute. You'll
notice all these AI UIs look very similar, and that's because they're based on another open
source project called a Gradio. And an interesting side note is that Gradio builds the front end
with Svelte. Pretty cool, but let's get started. Check out the install instructions, but basically
all you do is clone the repo, create a virtual environment for Python, and install the packages.
Once that's done, you run this Python script, which will then automatically download the default
models in the background. These files are multiple gigabytes large, so it may take a while. The base
model is Juggernaut XL, which is based on stable diffusion and works pretty well for realistic
images. You now have the power at your fingertips to prompt out any image you can imagine. The thing
I like about focus is that in many ways it feels similar to mid-journey, but it's free and the UI
is way more intuitive. I'm running it with a modest NVIDIA 3070, and it usually takes about 45
seconds to generate two quality images. What's really cool though is that if you click on the
Advanced tab, you'll get options for performance, aspect ratio, and the number of images. But there's
also a tab for style, and we can mix and match these different styles to get far different results,
like this retro video game style, or maybe an anime style. But in order to generate our AI influencer,
I'm going to go with the default settings along with focus, photograph, create a prompt that's
highly specific, and add some imperfections like rough skin, no makeup, etc. to make it more realistic.
And now our influencer is born. Now let's go ahead and save this as our base image, then create a
new prompt and check the box for input image. Drop the base image here to blend multiple images
and text together. Now click on the advanced box below the image to fine-tune the way the image is
blended. In this case we'll go with face swap and then write a text prompt of doing yoga at the
beach, giving us that perfect shot for the gram. But most importantly, we have pretty good continuity
between the faces, and the hands almost look totally realistic. But when you have imperfections,
you can go back to the image prompt, but this time go to in-paint or out-paint, and then paint across
the parts that are messed up. Tell it what you want to fix, then it will regenerate those parts of
the image. Congratulations, you just built your own artificial influencer. You did it! But photos
are only the beginning. Yesterday, Pika Labs released an insane video demoing their text-to-video
platform. It's closed source, but luckily stability AI just introduced stable diffusion video last week,
and I can only imagine what kind of depraved content you guys will use that for. This has
been The Code Report, thanks for watching, and I will see you in the next one.