BREAKING NEWS!
A local developer forgets how to iterate over a list in Java after five years of experience as a Java backend developer.
Witnesses say they were last seen frantically Googling how to increment an iterator in Java before vanishing into the abyss of Stack Overflow.
If you've ever felt like an absolute fraud despite, you know, actually writing code that works, congratulations, you have imposter syndrome.
And guess what? Every real developer has it.
If you don't wake up at least once a week thinking, wait, do I actually know how to code or have I just been faking it really well?
You're a phony!
Then you, my friend, are either a liar or an AI-generated LinkedIn guru.
Here's the thing, nobody actually knows what they're doing.
You think senior devs just know how everything works?
Nah, they're just better at Googling it without looking like they're Googling it.
Trust me, the same people who write billion dollar infrastructure still have to Google how to exit Vim.
And don't even get me started on centering a div.
Some of the smartest engineers in the world are out here losing battles to CSS like it's an Elden Ring boss fight.
Meanwhile, Chad from your boot camp is already pitching his AI-powered crypto startup.
Imposter syndrome is just part of being a developer.
A 2020 study found that over 58% of software engineers admit to feeling like frauds at some point in their careers.
The other, 42%, probably too scared to admit it.
Even Guido Van Rossum, the guy who literally invented Python, once said he doesn't always feel like he knows what he's doing.
So yeah, if the creator of an entire programming language feels like an imposter sometimes, you are definitely allowed to panic over a missing semicolon.
But here's the truth no one tells you. Tech moves too fast for anyone to actually keep up.
One day, you're a React expert. The next day, React announces React Quantum.
And suddenly you need to unlearn everything you've ever known.
JavaScript frameworks evolve faster than your ability to understand them.
The moment you finally get comfortable, boom. New release.
Everything's deprecated. And now you have to watch another 12-hour tutorial on YouTube just to feel like a functional human being again.
So if you ever feel like you don't know enough, remember, neither does anyone else.
The only difference between a junior and a senior dev, seniors are just better at hiding their Google searches.
You think that guy in the corner debugging a massive enterprise application isn't copy-pasting Stack Overflow solutions with his whole chest?
Think again. If you can write code, break code, then frantically search for why your code is broken, congratulations, you're a real developer.
And finally, if all else fails, just remember, you're only a fraud if you get caught.
Now excuse me while I google how to write a for loop again.
And don't forget to like and subscribe, or you will instantly forget how to center a div.
And these are debating.
So we're going to start seeing those differences in the day that's quite interesting.
And how to this going on.
So we can print back in.
So remember...
Then what happens to...
In our last minute, we're going to bring back into a wild dog and we could have its best.
The pattern of the mouse, you'll see a части of the mouse, it's that of courseВО Night sacks.
Theторовus, something that went along, you can see a kind where your pen is connected, and that it's a small of the mouse.
Of course we have.
So that the discovery is done.
Even if you're beginning this next time we're going to use the dog mode, man.
I think only really礙osis, not a good guy thing to do with you, and that didn't trust you.
And again, let's get caught up interestingly, it doesn't get me.